[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, Grandpa.
[SPEAKER_01]: How much is it?
[SPEAKER_00]: 58.
[SPEAKER_00]: 58?
[SPEAKER_00]: 30.
[SPEAKER_00]: 38.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
What are you checking on?
How cold is it here?
I think like minus five, six.
Maybe more than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's a deer.
Probably a deer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonny!
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, boy.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
So, what's the point of all this?
Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pssst!
[SPEAKER_02]: Phew!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sunny!
Eh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Ale ośmiem brakuje.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, those boards were cut.
[SPEAKER_00]: In this place, that's why it was closed, but not...
[SPEAKER_00]: Here, here it came out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Look, it's going to the basement, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sannyāsa.
[SPEAKER_02]: How's the smoke?
[SPEAKER_02]: There isn't any.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just egg-natural.
[SPEAKER_02]: Āyurī.